ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/081
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Legal Department Records
1919-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Legal Dept.
5780/081
45.56 cubic feet
45.6 linear ft.
Case files, agreements.
The collection consists of case files, case summaries, incomplete case files, contract histories, subject files and miscellaneous materials from the Legal Department between 1928 and 1982.
5492775
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 06, 2004
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 11, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
From very early on in its existence, the ILGWU had need for legal counsel, and this was handled in the union's main offices in cooperation with hired attorneys. As the union grew and especially after the passage of the Taft-Hartley Act in 1947, the union found cause to establish a Legal Department. The department provided general legal counsel to the union and its affiliates, worked to develop collective bargaining agreement terms, and represented the ILGWU in litigation and arbitration. After the formation of the Master Agreements Department in 1965, the responsibilities for developing CBA terms shifted to the new department.
Scope and Contents
The Legal Department records do not comprehensively document the ILGWU legal activities, instead focusing on specific cases or series of cases.
Two ILGWU cases are documented in the Legal Department records. The first case involved the Kellwood Corporation, and the second involved the Donnelly Garment Company. The records relating to the Kellwood case (5780/107, 5780/107 AV, 5780/107 P) include court documents, correspondence and memoranda, surveys of strikers, organizing leaflets and newsletters (from both the union and the company), Steve Honeyman's draft accounts of the strike, audio and transcripts of Honeyman's interviews with ILGWU members and staff, newspaper clippings, photographs, and other printed material. The Donnelly Garment Company's case against the ILGWU is documented primarily through transcripts of the case, legal briefs, and related court documents.
Records on series of cases are the most general and extensive of the Legal Department records. They include records on ILGWU cases in the U.S. courts (5780/081), records documenting cases before the National War Labor Board (5780/085), and records relating to a wide variety contract negotiations, arbitration proceedings, and courts cases (5780/063).
Researchers may find complementary material in the other parts of the ILGWU records, such as the papers of the international leadership, especially the papers of ILGWU presidents (Series IV); the records of local unions in instances where these affiliates were involved in litigation or arbitration (Series III); and the collective bargaining agreements (Series VI). Related collections at the Kheel Center include decisions of the Coat and Suit Industry's Impartial Chairman (6036/015) and decisions of the Dress Industry's Impartial Chairman (6036/017).
For the Legal Department records of 5780/081, the collection has been arranged into six series. Series I includes correspondence, legal documents, evidence, and memoranda relating to important cases from the 1950's to the early 1980's. Series II consists of case summaries composed of excerpts from reports of the Legal Department to the General Executive Board. Series III consists of incomplete case files on miscellaneous cases with little or no detail. Series IV consist of contract histories include correspondence and negotiations related to particularly critical agreements. Series V contains subject files dealing various aspects of union administration and internal affairs, especially with political finance, the Union Health Center and Unity House, arranged in alphabetical order. Series VI contains miscellaneous agreements.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/107: ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/107 AV: ILGWU Legal Department Audio-Visual Materials 5780/107 P: ILGWU Legal Department Photographs 5780/063: ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/162: ILGWU Legal Department Donnelly Garment Company v. ILGWU Records
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Legal Dept.
5492775
- A. Case Files (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence, legal documents, evidence, and memos relating to important cases from the 1950s to the early 1980s.
- Ash. Madden. Rae Company., 1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  10/19. Brief and argument for defendant in error.
- Basila Dress Company. [folder 1 of 3], 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  5/57-5/61.
- Basila Dress Company. [folder 2 of 3], 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Basila Dress Company. [folder 3 of 3], 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Baxley vs. Staub. General Correspondence., 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  3/54-3/55.
- Baxley vs. Staub. General Correspondence., 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  3/55-9/56.
- Baxley vs. Staub. General Correspondence., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  9/56-12/56.
- Baxley vs. Staub. General Correspondence., 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  12/56-6/57.
- Baxley vs. Staub. General Correspondence., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  6/57-9/57.
- Baxley vs. Staub. General Correspondence., 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  9/57-1/58.
- Baxley vs. Staub. General Correspondence., 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  1/58-5/62.
- Baxley vs. Staub. Briefs. [folder 1 of 2], 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  3/54-10/56.
- Baxley vs. Staub. Briefs. [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bernhard Altmann. General Correspondence., 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  8/57-4/58.
- Bernhard Altmann. General Correspondence., 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  4/58-3/60.
- Bernhard Altmann. General Correspondence., 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  3/60-2/61.
- Bernhard Altmann. General Correspondence., 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  2/61-1/63.
- Bernhard Altmann. File Memos., 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  8/57-1/61.
- Bernhard Altmann. Contract Materials., 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  6/57-9/60.
- Bernhard Altmann. Dun and Bradstreet Reports., 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  12/56-9/57.
- Bernhard Altmann. National Labor Relations Board cases., 1958-1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  7/58-5/62.
- Bernhard Altmann. Court of Appeals cases. [folder 1 of 2], 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  8/57-7/60.
- Bernhard Altmann. Court of Appeals cases. [folder 2 of 2], 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bernhard Altmann. Supreme Court case no.284., 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  7/60-6/61.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Wilbur Daniels' Files. [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  1/50-7/61.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Wilbur Daniels' Files. [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1961 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Elias Lieberman's Files. [folder 1 of 2], 1943-1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  3/43-7/61.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Elias Lieberman's Files. [folder 2 of 2], 1943-1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Full record of meetings and correspondence., 1949-1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  7/49-8/53. Anti-trust division of the Department of Labor re: collective agreements in the ladies' garment industry. Assembled by Emil Schlesinger.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Federal grand jury investigation and Local 25 (Minutes)., 1949-1959 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  10/49-4/59. Blouse and Waistmakers documents and agreements (for federal grand jury investigation).
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Local 25. [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  1/51-9/60.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Local 25. [folder 2 of 2], 1951-1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Minutes of meetings of the National Association of Blouse Manufacturers., 1949-1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  4/49-6/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Pleadings motions record., 1928-1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  2/28-9/47. Correspondence mainly between Elias Lieberman and Webster Ballinger.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence concerning agreements., 1959-1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  6/59-7/59.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Agreements., 1933-1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Agreements., 1941-1947 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Agreements., 1948-1953 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Agreements., 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Agreements., 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. ILGWU Constitution, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Model by-laws for District Councils, Northeast Department.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Memorandum Brief for Trial Examiner in the Matter of National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, et al. (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Respondents' Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law in the Matter of National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, et al. (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Respondents' Supplemental Statement Pursuant to Former Rule XXII and Present Rule XXI, and Respondents' Reply to the Memo Brief of Counsel for the Commission in the Matter of National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, et al. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Trial Examiner's Recommended Decision in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al.., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  1/48.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Various briefs and memos. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  2/26/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  2/27/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  2/28/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al. 3/3/47., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  3/3/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  3/10/47, 3/20/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  3/21/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  3/24/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  3/26/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  3/27/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  3/28/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  4/3/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  6/4/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  6/5/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  6/6/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  6/9/47, 8/14/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Official Report of Proceedings Before the Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc., et al., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  10/24/47.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. USA vs. Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors' Association, Inc., et al., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  5/29/59. Stenographer's minutes.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with David Dubinsky over related issues., 1947-1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  2/47-9/55.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with David Dubinsky over related issues., 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  11/55-3/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with David Dubinsky over related issues., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  3/58-4/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with David Dubinsky over related issues., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  4/58-5/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with David Dubinsky over related issues., 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  6/58-2/59.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with Eastern Out of Town Department over related issues., 1952-1958 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  4/52-1/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence about Japanese imports., 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  4/55-8/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with Dress Joint Board over related issues., 1954-1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  10/54-2/59.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with Jonathan Logan over related issues., 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  9/57-6/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with Marlene Blouse Company over related issues., 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  6/55-3/57.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with Northeastern Department over related issues. [folder 1 of 3], 1947-1958 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  9/47-8/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with Northeastern Department over related issues. [folder 2 of 3], 1947-1958 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with Northeastern Department over related issues. [folder 3 of 3], 1947-1958 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Correspondence with Louis Stulberg over related issues., 1956-1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  4/56-7/58.
- Blouse Anti-Trust. Miscellaneous., 1937-1964 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  5/37-9/64.
- Cohen and Seaview Dress Company vs. ILGWU., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  5/78.
- Connecticut Foundry. Briefs for Connecticut Foundry, ILGWU, and National Labor Relations Board., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Cotrell and Leonard. David Rosen's Files. [folder 1 of 4], 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  7/79-4/81.
- Cotrell and Leonard. David Rosen's Files. [folder 2 of 4], 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Cotrell and Leonard. David Rosen's Files. [folder 3 of 4], 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Cotrell and Leonard. David Rosen's Files. [folder 4 of 4], 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Cotrell and Leonard. David Rosen's handwritten notes. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 23)
  No dates, no order.
- Cotrell and Leonard. David Rosen's handwritten notes. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Correspondence between Samuel Rosen and Christopher Roach., 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  8/79-1/80.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Minutes of meetings of strikers., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  9/79-11/79.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Affidavits., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Includes Bernice Carey, Judy Conley, Gloria Gregory, Ronald Merrill, Sandra Monroe, Nancy Musella, and Richard Sewell.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Evidence. Employee counts, time cards, authorization card. (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Evidence. Employees' withholding allowance certificates. (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Exhibits. Charges, petitions, letters, and mailgrams. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Exhibits. Letters, newspaper articles, settlement. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Precedents. Ann Lee Sportswear. Daybreak Lodge Nursing. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Precedents. Douds vs. Milk Drivers. International Hod Carriers. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Precedents. Jacques Syl Knitwear vs. ILGWU. Peaker Run Coal Company. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Precedents. Polynesian Cultural Center. Westinghouse Electric Corporation. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Cotrell and Leonard. Legal documents., 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  9/79-8/80. Orders, complaints, stipulations of fact, subpoenas, settlement agreement.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Official Report of Proceedings Before the National Labor Relations Board. Cotrell and Leonard Company, Inc. and Local 163, ILGWU, AFL-CIO., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  8/4/80.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Official Report of Proceedings Before the National Labor Relations Board. Cotrell and Leonard Company, Inc. and Local 163, ILGWU, AFL-CIO., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  8/5/80.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Official Report of Proceedings Before the National Labor Relations Board. Cotrell and Leonard Company, Inc. and Local 163, ILGWU, AFL-CIO., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  8/6/80.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Official Report of Proceedings Before the National Labor Relations Board. Cotrell and Leonard Company, Inc. and Local 163, ILGWU, AFL-CIO., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  8/7/80.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Boycott campaign correspondence., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  1/80-9/80, undated.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Unemployment claims of strikers., 1960-1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  4/60, 5/73, 6/74, 5/78-6/80.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Vermont Industrial Development Authority (VIDA)., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  4/80-5/80. Correspondence about company's attempt to relocate.
- Cotrell and Leonard. Miscellaneous. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Donnelly Garment Company. Labor Board Case (Briefs in U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals). (Box 5, Folder 15a)
  1 bound volume.
- Donnelly Garment Company. Additional Briefs in Injunction Case. (Box 5, Folder 15b)
- Donnelly Garment Company. Briefs in U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals (Volume 6). (Box 5, Folder 15c)
- Donnelly Garment Company. Further Briefs in Injunction Case (Volume 7). (Box 5, Folder 15d)
- Donnelly Garment Company. Opinion of the U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals, Eighth Circuit., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  6/5/41.
- Donnelly Garment Company. Additional Briefs in Injunction Case (Volume 8). (Box 6, Folder 1a)
- Donnelly Garment Company. Briefs in U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals and Supreme Court of the U.S. (Volume 9). (Box 6, Folder 1b)
- Donnelly Garment Company. Abstract of the Record 9 (Volumes I-IX). (Box 6, Folder 1c)
  9 bound volumes.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Wilbur Daniels. General Correspondence., 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  5/55-10/58.
- Donnelly Garment Company. U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals Transcript of Record (Volumes 1-5). (Box 7, Folder 1d)
  5 bound volumes.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Wilbur Daniels. Manufacturer associations' ratification procedures and member liability., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Atlanta - Newark.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Wilbur Daniels. Manufacturer associations' ratification procedures and member liability., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  New York City - Winnipeg.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Wilbur Daniels. Contract clauses from various industries., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Morris Glushien. General Correspondence. [folder 1 of 2], 1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  7/55-10/63.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Morris Glushien. General Correspondence. [folder 2 of 2], 1955 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Morris Glushien's correspondence with other unions regarding contract clauses., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  6/56.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Lazare Teper. Correspondence., 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  11/53-6/56.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). List of evidence; list of respondents' exhibits. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Affidavit of Henry J. Moscowitz and Statement of Arthur J. Goldberg., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Evidence., 1954-1957 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Agreement between ILGWU, Los Angeles Cloak Joint Board, and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 994 with Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers' Association.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Evidence. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Compilation of agreement provisions relating to specific Federal Trade Commission complaints.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Morris Glushien's correspondence with other unions regarding contract clauses. [folder 1 of 2], 1956 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  6/56-8/56.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Evidence. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Constitution of California Apparel Contractors' Association; By-laws of Children's Dress, Cotton Dress, and Sportswear Contractors' Association.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Morris Glushien's correspondence with other unions regarding contract clauses. [folder 2 of 2], 1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Evidence. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Quotes, paragraphs, and clauses taken from books and articles (arranged by author).
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Files relating to issue of Federal Trade Commission's jurisdiction over labor unions. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Precedents. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Arranged in alphabetical order by case.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Precedents. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Precedents. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 8, Folder 13)